notice for next issue
My name is Funa Sasaki. Nice to meet you.
Fuuna-chan.
My name is Fuuna Sasaki.
I nominated you for the two-shot talk at Militon the other day.
Thank you very much.
In this corner, we took a questionnaire beforehand to find out what other members think about Fuu-chan.
What do you think they wrote?
Well, I think it's serious.
Serious things.
I want to believe that there is nothing bad in it.
I want to believe that.
Well then, I'd like to read everyone's answers right away.
The first question is, what was your impression when you first saw it?
What? I thought you didn't seem to have much of a presence.
I didn't write that.
Then, let's get right to it, Miku.
Miku's answer was that she was taller than I expected, and I didn't even realize Fuu-chan was there until she spoke to me.
She looked like a good singer.
It says she was a good singer after all.
But you knew that beforehand, didn't you? Miku.
Yes, Miku knew me at the distribution audition, but she was so tall that she didn't realize it was really me until she heard about it.
You realized it after talking to her?
Yes, I realized it when we were talking.
Now the second one, Arisa.
I thought she was a solid person.
I also thought she was a cool singer and dancer, and I wished I could be a solid person too.
The leader.
Leader? I didn't think so.
I was really firm, even though I said so myself. That's the image everyone has of me.
I guess I do feel that way.
Next is Miri.
I thought that you and Ryo-ka had been good friends since the audition and that you had always been friends.
That's not true.
Yes, but we met during the third round, and we both came in at the same time.
Final?
The third hour was also the final.
I see.
So I think we were pretty close.
I know that's a thing, isn't it...we were at the third round together, but I wasn't with anyone, and we all started.
I was nervous.
Next question.
Questionnaire: Describe Ms. Sasaki in one word.
Let's start with Monami's answer.
She always carries gummy bears with her.
She takes pictures of the gummies she eats and keeps a gummi diary.
Do you keep a diary?
Yes, I do.
Do you have a lot?
I reached the 40th one the other day.
Forty kinds.
When did you start?
Since January 31, a little over a month.
40 in a little over a month?
Forty.
That's more than one a day.
Do you get them from someone or from gummy bears that you are interested in?
Yes, I get them. And Ogawa, too.
That's right.
There are a lot of gummies.
When they were given to me.
I took pictures of everything.
Era.
That's me, next.
I may look quiet, but I have great potential.
I'm Kazuna Sasaki with glutinous cheeks.
There's a reason for that.
She has more potential than anyone else, and I think she is the one who supports the group behind the scenes.
She is indispensable to Rough Rough.
I'm glad.
You are so right.
I'm not the type of person who goes out and tells everyone what to do, but I feel that he supports us behind the scenes,
But I feel that he supports us behind the scenes.
I'm glad.
I didn't say anything.
Tell me, Fu-chan, if you hear my voice.
Next, Meinya.
Not just fluffy and cute. She is a bundle of ambition hidden inside.
She's a hard worker, which is hard to imagine from her soft and fluffy image.
Everyone is like this.
They may look fluffy on the outside, but they are working hard behind the scenes.
I'm so happy.
All I can say is I'm happy.
It's a happy corner.
I am happy.
Next, let's move on to Fu-chan, who only I know.
What do you say, Mr. Kugiki?
Yui Takanashi.
Yui Yui is a pampered little girl who sometimes gets super sweet on me.
There was a time when Fu-chan came to spoil me by burying her face in my shoulder,
The feeling of happiness at that time was one of the best in my life.
Yui Yui is getting so happy.
I'm so happy.
Do you want to?
Especially because YuiYui is like a big sister.
We're together quite a lot.We are together quite often, aren't we?
Yes, we do. I might get spoiled.
But it happens sometimes. At Kana's place.
Yes. I go there sometimes. She goes to everyone.
She's cute. She really is. I've never been older than you.
You don't think so?
Next, Miku.
I went to Katai's concert, and when the live seats were shown on the screen, Funa was there,
It also says that she was on youtube.
That's right.
When I went to the first anniversary concert, there was a digest of the concert on Youtube,
Miku was sure that she could see me doing this.
Miku found it too. She likes it too, right?
We were on LINE. She said, "Is this Funa-san's? Miku sent it to me?
Miku sent it to you? Did you notice? Until then.
I didn't know.
Tell her it's really me.
I wonder if she's popular with her fans.
You'll have to look for it.
Next, let's go to Arisachi.
She often sounds like a dolphin, like an ultrasonic wave.
Every time she does it, she sounds like a dolphin,
I always reply, "Oh, he's so cute.
Indeed. Really. I wrote this too.
When he becomes a nerd, he makes an amazing voice,
You make your voice so loud and high pitched that it sounds amazing.
I know, right? Monamiman, for example.
I'm always a nerd when it comes to monamins,
Like an ultrasound.
Please do it.
I won't do it.
I'm not going to do it.
I'll take some pictures next time.
I'll post it on social media or something.
Next, Miri.
Tokyo Anti. I'm going to run into the train and get on.
This is different.
It's different.
You're anti-Tokyo.
You're pretty much anti-transportation.
The river is dirty, isn't it?
No, no. Where is Tokyo dirty?
No, I might have said it's dirty.
You did.
I said it to Anna, too.
It's the same thing.
Running into the train and getting on it,
We were talking about it the other day.
When Miri and I were together.
I'm a slow learner, so I didn't want to get on the train.
I'm a lazy person, so I don't get on the train,
I was the only one who passed him.
I got on the train and was scared.
This way.
I sometimes see people getting caught in the train.
I'm afraid that you might get caught in the train someday.
I'm scared, so please don't do it.
Once I decide to do this, I want to accomplish it.
Once I decide to ride, I want to ride.
Next, Monami.
I tend to lose my wallet or miss the train several times in a week.
That's right. I have had the lost wallet incident.
About three times this year.
In this year? That was in March.
Really?
The first time I really lost it and found it at a convenience store,
The second time, I didn't realize I dropped it after entering the ticket gate,
The second time, I didn't realize I dropped it until after I entered the ticket gate, and an uncle told me I had dropped it.
That's great.
I didn't notice it. I had lost it twice.
I thought I had lost the other one, so I went back to the office,
But it ended up in the bottom of my backpack.
I'll check it out.
But this one time was amazing.
It was a big commotion.
I called many places and asked if they had it. I was calling all kinds of places to ask if they had it.
You made a lot of calls, didn't you?
Thank God it was there.
Where?
I'm sorry.
I tend to miss trains.
Do you?
I must have fallen asleep.
I often fall asleep.
Especially right before a test because it was the last stop,
I was asleep and didn't notice that the train had stopped,
I was sleeping, and the Sweleman asked me, "Are you okay? I was so thankful.
I was so grateful. Ordinary Maria.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad.
Next question.
Is there anything you honestly want me to fix?
I'm curious.
Arisatchi. The nighttime miming.
I want you to be careful not to rinse out your mimicry at night because it kills your voice.
The dolphin one, maybe.
It's almost the same way as the dolphins.
I really broke my throat once at night.
I broke it.I broke it.
When I came back from a trip to junior high school, my voice was gassy from the voice training,
When the teacher asked him why, he told her that he did too many imitations at night.
Everyone has a variety of skills, don't they? Like techniques.
I have a belly.
Like the mononami beam.
I thought, "I don't have anything, so I wondered what it was,
I thought, "This could work." That's how I came up with the nighttime mimicry.
You practiced?
Yes, I did.
Then I broke my throat.
I broke my throat.
Please stop.
I want to stop.
Okay. Next, Monami.
I, so you must be Monami.
When I talk with Monami, my voice is almost always in a mosquito tone and I can't hear what we are talking about.
It says here that the members around her are worried about her.
Monami is the same, isn't she?
Monami is the same.
Monami is also talking in Mosquito Tone.
I'm talking in Mosquito Tone.
What's a Mosquito Tone? A cutthroat voice.
A high voice.
High pitched voice.
Is that what you mean?
Yeah.
It's a voice that comes out for sure.
It's like she's saying she's cute or something.
That's what I meant.
I'm really worried about it.
You're both talking about the same voice.
I'm glad you're worried about me.
Next, Riryu.
She wants me to fix the part of me that is so kind that I put myself on the back burner because I'm too concerned about the people around me.
That's not true.
I'm too careful.
Thank you very much.
You are very kind.
You're Ritsure-san, right?
Next, me.
Sometimes he touches my cheek, which in itself is nice, but I promised to touch him after discharging static electricity because it comes every time.
But he tried to touch my eyes.
Do you want me to get a buzz?
Yes, I did.
I'm sure it's a hassle, you know,
I'm not interested.
You're the one in pain. All the time.
Whenever Miku touches me, like when we dance, I get a buzzing sound, so I remembered that maybe I'm the problem.
Next time, do you want me to try it too?
Let's both discharge.
And touch.
OK.
Lastly, I want to say something. I'd like to say something since we're here.
Arisatchi.
What gummy bears do you recommend?
I want to know too.
Gummy recommendations?
I'm so confused.
No, but the collaboration between Pil Gummi and Maroche was really shocking, after all,
It was delicious.
I just want you to try them,
After all, idols need to be on a diet, don't they?
And, of course, ninja rice.
Is it good?
It only has 66 calories.
Are gummy bears really expensive?
Yes, they are. They are usually over 100.
It's not that bad.
Ninja rice.
I've never seen tens of calories in them.
Is it good?
It tastes good.
And it's hard, so you feel like you've eaten.
That's for sure. Yes, it does.
They say that if you chew it, you feel full.
That's why,
I recommend it.
And to all the fans, too.
Ninja rice for weight loss.
Ninja rice for dieting.
I'm like, "Diet, eat ninja rice.
Next. Miri.
What?
Isn't Tokyo a bad place?
It's not that I don't like Tokyo.
I heard it's not a bad place.
Tokyo is not a bad place.
I admit it.
Let's admit it. Tokyo is a good place.
Okay, next. Mei-chan.
There's nothing you haven't done as much as you think.
She's just amazing, but she's growing up more and more.
It's just so cool.
Don't cry.
I'll cry.
You'll cry? Your eyes are all oriole.
I'm so happy.
Thank you, everyone.
Next. Monami.Next. Monami.
I've often wondered whether to part my bangs or leave them as they are,
You look good no matter what you do.
By the way, my favorite haircut that you did was a loosely curled bun.
Indeed.
The one from the magazine shoot.
I'm glad.
I don't have to worry about bangs.
You ask me about bangs every day, don't you? Someone asks me.
Do you think I should split them?
Which one do you like better? I don't know.
They're both cute.
I'll decide for myself.
I guess that's it then.
So how was your first T-shirt talk?
Impressive.
I'm a little on the way to becoming a man of the hour.
And don't do the night thing.
He said he'll only take one picture of me and put it on social media.
I'll do it later.
Please do it later.
It's a relay format, so who would you like to interview?
Please do.
Yui Yui.
Yui yui, right? We're good friends.
Next, we will have a two-shot talk between Fu-chan and Yui Yui.
That's all for the members' relay talk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I am very happy to have been here.